tamrieltradecentre.com 2016-01-13

# Privacy Policy - Tamriel Trade Centre

##  Tamriel Trade Centre Privacy Policy 

* * *

Last modified: Nov 30, 2016 

The following terminology applies to all following agreements: "Client", "You" and "Your" refers to you - the person accessing this website. "Our", "Ourselves", "We" and "Us" refers to our Company(Website). 

This page informs you of our policies regarding the collection, use and disclosure of personal information we receive from you. By using this site, you agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this policy. 

####  Information you give us 

We collect and store some of your personal information during account registration such as your email address and Game UID 

####  Cookies 

Like many site operators, this website uses cookies to enable us to retrieve user data for each visit. Cookies are used in most areas of our site to uniquely identify you. If you do not accept cookies, you may not be able to use some portions of our site 

####  Google Analytics 

This site uses Google Analytics to collect web trafic data. Like many serviecs, Google Analytics uses cookie to store user data.   
For more about "How Google uses data when you use our partners' sites or apps" please visit <http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/>   
You can choose to opt out of Google Analytics without affecting your use of this site. For more information please visit <https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout>

####  Google Adsense 

Advertisements on this site are provided by Google Adsense.   
Third party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on a your prior visits to this website.   
Google uses DoubleClick cookie to enables it and its partners to serve ads to you based on your visit to this site and/or other sites on the Internet.   
You may opt out of the use of the DoubleClick cookie for interest-based advertising without affecting your use of this site by visiting [Google Ads Settings](http://www.google.com/ads/preferences/)   
Third-party vendors and ad networks may be serving ads on this site, you can choose to opt out of some third-party vendor's use of cookies for interest-based advertising without affecting your use of this site by visiting [aboutads.info](http://www.aboutads.info/)

####  Log Information 

Like many site operators, we collect information sent from your browser or software provided by us whenever you use our service. This log data may include information such as your Internet Protocal(IP) address, browser information, pages of our site that you visit, time of your visit, and event information such as crashes or unexpected errors. 

####  Security 

The security of your personal information is important to you and to us, we will try to protect your personal information as best as we can. But we cannot guarentee the absolute security of your personal information. 

####  Changes to This Privacy Policy 

Our Privacy Policy may change from time to time. We will post any updated privacy policy on this page. You are advised to review this Privacy Policy periodically for any changes.
